const js_question = {
    q1: {
        question: ' What does HTML stand for?',
        options: [
            'Hyper Text Markup Language',
            'Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language',
            'Home Tool Markup Language',
            'Hyper Text Mockup Language'
        ],
        answer: 'Hyper Text Markup Language',
    },
    q2: {
        question: ' Which meta tag is used to configure display for mobile devices?',
        options: [
            'handheld',
            'viewport',
            'mobile',
            'screen'
        ],
        answer: 'viewport',
    },
    q3: {
        question: ' Which of the following graphic types is well-suited to photographs?',
        options: [
            'JPG and WebP',
            'JPG ',
            'WebP',
            'GIF'
        ],
        answer: 'JPG and WebP',
    },
    q4: {
        question: ' Which of the following can be a CSS selector?',
        options: [
            'An HTML element name',
            'A class name',
            'An id name',
            'All of the above'
        ],
        answer: 'All of the above',
    },
    q5: {
        question: ' Which of the following describes the appearance of text within a th element?',
        options: [
            'The text is centered ',
            'The text is displayed one size larger',
            'The text has bold font weight',
            'The text has bold font weight and is centered'
        ],
        answer: 'The text has bold font weight and is centered',
    },
    q6: {
        question: 'Which tag pair is used to link web pages to each other?',
        options: [
            '<link> </link>',
            '<hyperlink> </hyperlink>',
            '<a> </a>',
            '<body> </body>'
        ],
        answer: '<a> </a>',
    },
    q7: {
        question: 'Which of the following is known as white space?',
        options: [
            'the empty screen area around blocks of text and images',
            'the background color of white used for a pag',
            'configuring the color of the text to be white',
            'none of the above'
        ],
        answer: 'the empty screen area around blocks of text and images'
    },
    q8: {
        question: 'Which of the following properties configures empty space between grid tracks?',
        options: [
            'align',
            'grid-gap',
            'gutter',
            'grid-template'
        ],
        answer: 'grid-gap'
    },
    q9: {
        question: 'Which HTML tag pair is used to specify table headings?',
        options: [
            '<td> </td>',
            '<th> </th>',
            '<head> </head>',
            '<tr> </tr>'
        ],
        answer: '<th> </th>'
    },
    q10: {
        question: 'Which CSS pseudo-class applies to the first element of a specified type?',
        options: [
            ':first-of-type',
            ':first-type',
            ':first-child',
            ':first'
        ],
        answer: ':first-child'
    },
}